<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mastermind Club Blog</title>
    <description>The Mastermind of Entrepreneurial Real Estate Agents Who Share Their 7-and-8 Figure Plans and Strategies...So You Too Can Grow Your Business with Ease In a Way That Makes You Happy</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 17:31:47 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 17:31:47 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spring shared how she went from $1.5 to $3.0 million in 2 years</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mastermind Club friends,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our member, Spring Bengtzen, spoke for an hour at our last meeting about how she doubled her business from $1.5 to $3.0 million GCI with unique recruiting strategies &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her team was about 4-5 agents a few years ago. They kept leaving “every 2 years or so”. She didn’t have a bench to replace her agents that left, so every time she had to start her recruiting process from scratch. This obviously took a toll on her and held her business back. I think many of you can relate to her story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/spring1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;639&quot; height=&quot;427&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what’s really cool about Spring…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She shared the recruiting marketing system she put in place at our last mastermind meeting. &lt;strong&gt;Now, she’s on pace to close $100 million with her top agent earning more than $250,000.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, that is a &lt;em&gt;confirmed&lt;/em&gt; number. I check MLS and bookkeeping records (assuming the client isn’t cooking their books) to make sure this is correct. I know people throw these around a lot and are not legit. You won’t get that from me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;She also hasn’t had an agent leave in over a year!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spring broke her recruiting marketing down into 3 core pillars, which she gave us permission to share with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Training website&lt;/strong&gt;. She has an agent training-focused website. You can see Spring’s at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.utahrealestatecareers.com/about&quot;&gt;https://www.utahrealestatecareers.com/about&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook ads.&lt;/strong&gt; She runs Facebook advertisements to drive applicants. Spring uses causal agent testimonials, video courses, and personal growth videos as her ad content. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Local events.&lt;/strong&gt; Spring drives all this attention to in-person events. She holds about one event a month to keep a pipeline alive she can recruit from. Her last event had 100+ people!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/spring2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would love to introduce you to Spring, or any member or guest so you can build a lasting business relationship with them. That’s my job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s what we’re all about. It’s what makes us different than a conference or seminar. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have four meetings scheduled this year. No more than 25 people a meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re welcome to join us if you earn&lt;em&gt; at least&lt;/em&gt; $425,000 GCI or sell 75 homes a year; however many here sell much more than that. You’ll send us the last 12 months of your MLS production to verify your attendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our meeting dates for this year are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;March 26-27&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;May 14-15&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;September 24-25&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;October 22-23&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call me at (619) 500-6563 or email me at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:peter@mastermindclub.us&quot;&gt;peter@mastermindclub.us&lt;/a&gt; if you’d like to join us. We allow 25 agents per meeting, with no more than 1 person in a market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A guest ticket is $700 which breaks us even together on the meeting. I share a P/L at the meeting so everyone who comes can see where the money went.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;you-can-learn-more-about-mastermind-club-and-what-were-all-about-here&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mastermindclub.us/&quot;&gt;You can learn more about Mastermind Club® and what we’re all about here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/spring-shared-how-she-went-from-1-5-to-3-0-million-in-2-years.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/spring-shared-how-she-went-from-1-5-to-3-0-million-in-2-years.html</guid>
        
        <category>Spring Bengtzen</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2020 Mastermind Club Dates!</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;visit-the-website-to-submit-your-interest&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mastermindclub.us/?utm_campaign=Real%20Estate%20Agent&amp;amp;utm_source=hs_email&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz-9PW6zb4fyqkP6FLbuLR21unZ559e0ZV-DDXype9U5jQ9M1HI4Bp8mY6QrmMHivMCBytItG&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Visit the website to submit your interest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real estate clients and friends,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you planning your 2020 travel dates like me right now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mastermind Club meetings this year are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;March 26-27&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;May 14-15&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;September 24-25&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;October 22-23&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are all in downtown San Diego at University Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talk to me about a guest invite if you’re seeking a smaller venue where you can &lt;em&gt;build relationships&lt;/em&gt; with really smart top producers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A ticket is $700. You can come to any one of our meetings as a guest if someone in your market isn’t already booked for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t allow any competitors in the room because, obviously, sensitive insight is being shared with the group by all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2-day meeting costs us $17,500 to do right. We divide it equally between the 25 people who join us. (I give you a P/L at the meeting)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We pay for all the meals and entertainment so we stay together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We bring together &lt;em&gt;business people who happen to sell real estate&lt;/em&gt; to share what’s working now and to help each other with our goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I would love for you to make a meeting&lt;/strong&gt;. Talk to me about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn2.hubspot.net/hubfs/2433991/MastermindClub/The%20Perfect%20Mastermind%20Agenda.pdf?utm_campaign=Real%20Estate%20Agent&amp;amp;utm_source=hs_email&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz-9PW6zb4fyqkP6FLbuLR21unZ559e0ZV-DDXype9U5jQ9M1HI4Bp8mY6QrmMHivMCBytItG&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Here’s the agenda&lt;/a&gt; (PDF). No, it’s not perfect. We tweak it a bit each time to get it just right. The point is we have a really good plan to run these well for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We allow 1 agent per available market with a 75 unit / $425k GCI production minimum. We limit the size to 25 people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not a conference, seminar, or workshop. This is a pure &lt;em&gt;mastermind&lt;/em&gt;. We’re here to learn deeply from each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone at the meeting is a speaker - you’ll have 10 minutes to share one thing that’s made you a lot of money with your peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of topic tables, group discussions, thinking tools, presentations, and networking breaks too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re interested, email me &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:frank@getvyral.com&quot;&gt;frank@getvyral.com&lt;/a&gt; or submit your interest on the website.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll have you speak with Peter, our Membership Chair, for an interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll explain what we’re all about and if attending makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll also get a list of who will be in the room with you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll be very impressed the talent we attract. In our first meeting last year, the combined home sales were over &lt;em&gt;3,000 homes a year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also at every meeting (of course) leading it as your facilitator and host. I would love to get some one-on-one time with you, too. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you make a meeting this year?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Frank&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. I have a great tip I’m recording tomorrow on “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;How do I generate seller leads with cold email?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expect it shortly. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been posting more Q&amp;amp;A videos. I’m wrapping up December’s client theme on &lt;em&gt;building&lt;/em&gt; your database of legitimate seller opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I answered these questions last month:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What’s the #1 best Facebook ad for seller lead generation?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How do I hire a telemarketer to generate seller leads for me legally?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What’s the best direct mail letter for seller lead generation?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How do I get a mailing or phone list of homeowners likely to sell?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.getvyral.com/blog/topic/weekly-training?utm_campaign=Real%20Estate%20Agent&amp;amp;utm_source=hs_email&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz-9PW6zb4fyqkP6FLbuLR21unZ559e0ZV-DDXype9U5jQ9M1HI4Bp8mY6QrmMHivMCBytItG&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;You can get all the answers here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s how you get seller leads into your database with marketing so you can nurture them with helpful, educational videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Topics: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.getvyral.com/blog/topic/mastermind-club&quot;&gt;Mastermind Club&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-mastermind-club-dates.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-mastermind-club-dates.html</guid>
        
        <category>Mastermind Dates</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Team Lally Landed a $1 Million Buyer Referral From a Bank</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mastermind Club friends,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to write you about a &lt;strong&gt;profitable connection&lt;/strong&gt; that was made from our last mastermind…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Members Adrienne and Attilio (Team Lally) are &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; top agents in Hawaii. They came to our meeting in November. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was given permission to share what they implemented, including the results from their time invested in “sharping the axe” with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Adrienne sent a “Hey” text to old leads with a great response rate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brian Burds shared a neat tip to get “unable to contact” leads to respond to you. He said “Just send a ‘Hey’ text to your leads”. Adrienne had her 4 person ISA team text 200 “bottom of the barrel” leads in their database this super simple message. Their response rate was 37.5%! It got people engaged with them again. &lt;em&gt;This can be an easy thing to get people interacting with you who have gone dark.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Attilio landed a $1.3 million buyer referral from his new bank&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jay Bourgana shared all his lead generation pillars at the mastermind. His most creative pillar is holding relationships with loan officers at banks to generate buyer referrals. Most large institutions, apparently, don’t have a process to pass off pre-approved buyers to real estate agents. Attilio was opening a checking account in Hawaii a week later when he asked the bank manager “Who do you send pre-approved buyers to?” &lt;em&gt;That one question landed him a $1.3 million dollar buyer referral right on the spot!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Adrienne and Attilio are now going to develop a $30 million land project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shawn O’Neill shared details on how private investor real estate syndication works. So, instead of selling 5 lots of land Adrienne and Attilio currently represent for a sales commission, they are now working to find private real estate syndicate money to finance the work to build it out! They are talking to Shawn for financing insight and referrals. &lt;em&gt;The entire project is a $30 million dollar project they are taking on!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would love for you to make these profitable connections, too! This is my role in Mastermind Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We have four meetings scheduled for next year&lt;/strong&gt;. You are welcome to join us as a guest if you earn at least $425k GCI or sell 75 homes a year, which is our minimum to be in the room.The meetings for next year are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;March 26-27&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;May 14-15&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;September 24-25&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;October 22-23&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call me at (619)500-6563 or email me at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:peter@mastermindclub.us&quot;&gt;peter@mastermindclub.us&lt;/a&gt; if you’d like to join us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/team-lally-landed-a-1-million-buyer-referral-from-a-bank.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/team-lally-landed-a-1-million-buyer-referral-from-a-bank.html</guid>
        
        <category>Team Lally</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
