<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title> Real Estate Podcast with </title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from  - your professional  Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor></managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2020-02-28 17:13:51 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright></media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email></itunes:email>
      <itunes:name></itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author></itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the  Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from  - your professional  Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spring shared how she went from $1.5 to $3.0 million in 2 years</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/spring-shared-how-she-went-from-1-5-to-3-0-million-in-2-years.html</link>
        
          <category>Spring Bengtzen</category>
        
        <author></author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-11 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>Mastermind Club friends,

Our member, Spring Bengtzen, spoke for an hour at our last meeting about how she doubled her business from $1.5 to $3.0 million GCI with unique recruiting strategies 

Her team was about 4-5 agents a few years ago. They kept leaving “every 2 years or so”. She didn’t have a bench to replace her agents that left, so every time she had to start her recruiting process from scratch. This obviously took a toll on her and held her business back. I think many of you can relate to her story.



Here’s what’s really cool about Spring…

She shared the recruiting marketing system she put in place at our last mastermind meeting. Now, she’s on pace to close $100 million with her top agent earning more than $250,000.

Yes, that is a confirmed number. I check MLS and bookkeeping records (assuming the client isn’t cooking their books) to make sure this is correct. I know people throw these around a lot and are not legit. You won’t get that from me.

She also hasn’t had an agent leave in over a year!

Spring broke her recruiting marketing down into 3 core pillars, which she gave us permission to share with you.


  Training website. She has an agent training-focused website. You can see Spring’s at https://www.utahrealestatecareers.com/about
  Facebook ads. She runs Facebook advertisements to drive applicants. Spring uses causal agent testimonials, video courses, and personal growth videos as her ad content. 
  Local events. Spring drives all this attention to in-person events. She holds about one event a month to keep a pipeline alive she can recruit from. Her last event had 100+ people!




I would love to introduce you to Spring, or any member or guest so you can build a lasting business relationship with them. That’s my job.

That’s what we’re all about. It’s what makes us different than a conference or seminar. 

We have four meetings scheduled this year. No more than 25 people a meeting.

You’re welcome to join us if you earn at least $425,000 GCI or sell 75 homes a year; however many here sell much more than that. You’ll send us the last 12 months of your MLS production to verify your attendance.

Our meeting dates for this year are:


  March 26-27
  May 14-15
  September 24-25
  October 22-23


Call me at (619) 500-6563 or email me at peter@mastermindclub.us if you’d like to join us. We allow 25 agents per meeting, with no more than 1 person in a market.

A guest ticket is $700 which breaks us even together on the meeting. I share a P/L at the meeting so everyone who comes can see where the money went.

You can learn more about Mastermind Club® and what we’re all about here.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our member, Spring Bengtzen, spoke for an hour at our last meeting about how she doubled her business from $1.5 to $3.0 million GCI with unique recruiting strategies.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author></itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our member, Spring Bengtzen, spoke for an hour at our last meeting about how she doubled her business from $1.5 to $3.0 million GCI with unique recruiting strategies.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in , home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright></copyright>
    <media:credit role="author"></media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from  - your professional  Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
